Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Ana, take my car.
I gave you the recorder right?
- Oh, yes.
- And you have all the questions?
- Yes.
- And you know where you're going?
Yes, I do have a GPS, and a four point GPA.
- I can figure it out.
- You're wearing that?
Okay, a little less talking, more eating.
Miss Kavanagh?
- May I take your coat?
- Oh, yes.
Uh... She's... Okay.
- Mr Grey will see you now - Okay.
- This way please.
- Okay.
Mr Grey is in a conference at 11:15.
Right this way.
Miss Kavanagh, are you alright?
Christian Grey.
I'm Anastasia Steele.
Miss Kavanagh has the flu, so she asked me to fill in.
I see, so you're studying journalism as well?
No. English literature. Kate's my roommate.
As I said, I only have 10 minutes.
Please, have a seat Miss Steele.
Thanks.
- Ready?
- Whenever you are.
Okay.
So this is for the special graduation issue
of the student newspaper.
Yes, I'm giving the commencement address
at this year's ceremony.
You are?
I mean um... I know.
You are very young to have amassed such empire.
- To what do you owe...
- To what do I owe my success?
- Yep.
- Seriously?
Yes.
Business is about people, and I've always been good at people.
What motivates them, what incentivizes them, what inspires them.
Well, maybe you're just lucky.
I've always found, the harder I work, the more luck I seem to have.
The key to my success is identifying talents in individuals.
- And harnessing their efforts.
- You're a control freak?
Oh, I exercise control in all things, Miss Steele.
Okay... um, your company is involved primarily
in the telecommunications sector.
Yet you also invest in numerous agricultural projects.
Including several in Africa. Is that something you feel passionate about?
Feeding the world's poor?
Its smart business.
You don't agree?
I don't know enough about it.
I just wonder, perhaps your heart might be a bit bigger than you want to let on?
But some people say I don't have a heart.
- Why would they say that?
- Because they know me well.
Continue.
Do you have any interests outside of work?
I enjoy various physical pursuits.
You're unmarried, oh, you were adopted at age four.
That's a matter of public record.
I'm sorry, I didn't...
Do you have an actual question, Miss Steele?
Yes, sorry.
Are you gay?
Its written here, I'm just...
No, Anastasia. I'm not gay.
I apologise, Mr Grey. Kate can be a little...
- Intrusive?
- Curious.
What about you?
Why don't you ask me something you wanna know?
Earlier you said that there are some people who know you well.
Why do I have the feeling that that is not true?
Mr Grey, your next meeting is in the conference room.
Cancel it please, we're not finished here.
Yes sir.
No, I um... I can go.
- Its fine.
- I would like to know more about you.
There's not really much to know about me.
You said you're in English literature?
Tell me, was it Charlotte Bront?, Jane Austen
or Thomas Hardy, who made you fall in love with literature?
Hardy.
I would've guessed Jane Austen.
What are your plans for after you graduate?
I'm just trying to get through my finals.
- And then?
- Then I was planning on moving here.
To Seattle with Kate.
We offer an excellent internship program.
I don't think I'd fit in here.
- Look at me.
- I am.
Mr Grey's office.
I hope you got everything you needed.
I think you only answered four questions.
- Anastasia.
- Christian.
Holy cow!
Before you say anything... You're a goddess, this is perfect.
What?
I just got his email, he answered every question.
So? What was he like?
- He was fine.
- Fine? Just fine?
He was very polite, and he was curteous, and very formal and clean.
Clean?
I mean, he was very you know, smart.
And intense, kind of intimidating.
- I can understand the fascination.
- Uh huh!
- Why are you looking at me like that?
- Like what?
Okay.
I'm gonna make a sandwich, do you want one?
No, thanks.
You have to admit, he's ridiculously hot.
I'm sure if you're attracted to that sort of human.
The hot type of human?
I asked him if he was gay. It was in your questions.
Why would you do that to me?
Because whenever he's in the society pages.
He's never been photographed with a woman so naturally.
Well maybe he just wants to keep his private life private, Kate.
- And now you're defending him.
- I'm ending this conversation.
Too bad we don't have any original stills of your
hot, clean, 27 year old billionaire.
The camera loves him as much as you do.
Okay I wasn't hungry, but now I am.
Thank you.
I love you.
- Ana, I've been looking for you.
- Whats up?
- Guess what?
- What?
Portland's place is going to exhibit my photographs next month.
Oh my god!
Congratulations, thats so good!
- It feels so good.
- Can we celebrate later?
Cause I'm really late for work.
Yeah, yeah, you got it, you got it.
- Hold on, hold on, hold on...
- Thank you, you're my hero.
- See you later.
- Okay.
Mom I'm at work, can I call you back?
No wait. I called for a reason.
Bob broke his foot playing golf of all things.
Christ, is he okay? Is he in a lot of pain?
Who knows? The man called the paramedics because of a blister.
It means though, we won't be able to fly in for graduation.
Really? I mean, you could just come alone, you don't have to bring Bob.
Leave "Tiger" Woods to defend for himself?
- You understand, don't you darling?
- Yeah, yeah its fine.
- I really have to go, okay?
- I love you, Ana.
I know, I love you too.
God.
- Ana! Can you give me a hand out back?
- Uh yeah yeah, I'll be right there.
- Thought it was you.
- What the...?
What a pleasant surprise. Miss Steele.
It's Ana, just Ana. You're in here...
I was in the area on business, needed to pick up a few things.
- Are you free?
- Yeah. What can I help you with?
Do you stock cable ties?
Cable ties, yes we do, I can show you if you want.
- Please, lead the way, Miss Steele.
- Its Ana.
- That it?
- Masking tape.
- Are you redecorating?
- No.
We have two inch and one inch, but the truly self respecting handyman
would have both in his tool box.
Of course he will.
It's rare to find a connoisseur these days...
- Do you want anything else?
- Yes, rope.
That's very impressive. You're girl scout?
No, organised group activity aren't really my thing.
- So what is your thing?
- I don't know... Books?
Okay, rope, tape, cable ties. You're like a complete serial killer.
- Not today.
- Anything else?
- What would you recommend?
- For a do-it-yourself er?
Maybe coveralls, to protect all your clothes?
- Or I could just take all my clothes off.
- Okay, no clothes.
I mean, no coveralls. I can't ever think of anything else.
- Well, I guess that's it then.
- Cool.
Thank you for answering Kate's questions by the way.
- She was thrilled.
- I hope she's feeling better.
She is. Yeah, much. She's just having a hard time clearing a photo of you again.
If she'd like an original, I'm around tomorrow.
- You'd be willing to do that?
- Yeah.
Do you want me to bag for you, Ana?
No, No, I'm good, thanks though, Paul.
Okay.
I'm staying locally at the Heathman. Call me before 10.
- About the photos.
- Oh, yeah, I will.
Enjoy your...
Thanks again for doing this, Mr Grey.
- I'm happy to help.
- How about we try a few with a smile?
Or... or not.
You do realise he hasn't stopped looking at you?
He asked me to go for a coffee afterwards.
What?
Kate, shh...
So is he your boyfriend?
- Who?
- The photographer.
- Jose? No.
- I saw the way he was smiling at you.
No, Jose is more like family. He's not my boyfriend.
- And the guy at the store?
- Paul? No.
Thank you.
- You seem nervous.
- I find you intimidating.
You should.
- Eat.
- Not to mention high-handed.
I'm used to getting my own way.
That must get very boring.
- Tell me about your family.
- My family? Uh... Okay.
My dad died when I was a baby.
So I was raised by my step-father, Ray.
- He's amazing.
- And your mother?
My mother is on husband number four.
She's an incurable romantic.
- Are you?
- Am I romantic?
Well, I study English Lit. So I kind of have to be.
I thought the photo shoot went well, right? Kate seems to be really happy.
- I'm sorry, I can't.
- What?
I'll walk you out.
- Do you have a girlfriend, is that it?
- I don't do the girlfriend thing.
- What does that even mean?
- Watch it!
I'm not the man for you. You should steer clear of me.
I have to let you go.
Goodbye, Mr Grey.
Alright, pencils down.
Please take your final exams to the back of the classroom.
Final grades will be posted in two weeks.
- Hey, you all good?
- Yeah, why wouldn't I be?
- We are so partying tonight!
- Oh my god.
This is way too much.
No, we're getting exactly the right amount.
- All over my face?
- That's the idea.
- Wow, no, Kate.
- Cab's early, let's go.
Ana, there's a package for you.
Why didn't you tell me there was danger? Why didn't you warn me?
Ladies know what to guard against
because they read novels that tells them of these tricks.
That's a quote from Tess of the d'Urberville.
Oh my god.
These must be from Christian.
I mean...
These are incredible.
Wow, Grey.
Kate, these are first editions. I can't, this is too much.
I can't accept these, I have to send them back.
That's the cab, okay, are you ready?
- Are you really, though?
- Yes, yes, very.
Let's get outta here.
Shots! Shots! Shots!
No holding back here girl!
- Did you do it all?
- Alright!
With my right eye closed and left handed, I can get this in.
- What?
- I gotta pee.
- Okay.
- One, two...
- Where you going?
- I gotta go pee.
Christian Grey.
- Anastasia.
- Yep, this is me.
Sending back your expensive books,
cause I already have hard copies of that.
Thanks though, for the kind gesture.
You're welcome. Where are you?
Oh? I'm in line, cause I have to pee really bad.
Anastasia, have you been drinking?
Yeah, I have, Mr Fancy Pants.
You hit the nail on the head.
I mean the head right on the nail.
Listen to me, I want you to go home right now.
You're so bossy.
"Ana, lets go for coffee", "Ana, lets go for coffee."
"No stay away from me Ana, I don't want you, get away."
"Come here, come here." "Go away."
Thats it.
- Tell me where you are.
- I'm a long way from Seattle.
- Long way from you.
- Which bar, whats it called?
- I don't know, I gotta go.
- Which bar, Ana?
I told him right?
Christian Grey.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean...
Stay where you are, I'm coming to get you.
What? Hello?
- Hey.
- Oh thanks.
Are you okay?
Yes, I just feel a little more drunk than...
- Come here, stay warm.
- Oh thats cool, I'm good, Jose.
No, I wanna have the courage to do this.
Do what?
- Ana, I like you.
- You do?
- Very much.
- Oh my god.
- No, no, no.
- Please, one kiss.
No, no, no. Jose, I'm sorry, no.
- Dude, she said no.
- Christian?
- Don't look at me.
- Here.
Nice touch, I will launder this item.
- Lets get you home.
- I'm with Kate.
- I'll have Elliot tell her.
- Who's Elliot?
He's my brother, he's inside talking to her right now.
- I, I don't...
- He's at my hotel with me.
- You're still at the Heathman?
- Yes. Come.
- Thats your brother?
- Not by choice, let's go.
Wait, what did Kate say?
She warned me to be on my best behaviour.
- More like threatened me.
- She threatened you?
You're spinning. I think I'm gonna faint.
What, now?
Eat me, drink me.
Good morning, Anastasia.
- How you feeling?
- Better than I deserve.
Did you put me to bed?
- You undressed me?
- I didn't have much choice.
Where did you sleep?
Oh my god... Did we? We didn't...
Necrophillia's not my thing.
- So we just slept then?
- It was a novelty for me too.
You... need to eat. I had Taylor pick you up some clothes.
- Who's Taylor?
- My driver.
Thanks, but you didn't have to do that.
Yes I did.
Yours were covered in vomit.
You shouldn't have drunk like that.
I'm all for testing the limits but...
- you put yourself at risk last night.
- I know.
If you were mine, you wouldn't be able to sit down for a week.
What?
I gotta go take a shower.
Why am I here, Christian?
You're here because I'm incapable of leaving you alone.
Then don't.
- Why'd you send me those books?
- I thought I owed you an apology.
- For what?
- For letting you believe that I...
Listen to me. I don't do romance.
My tastes are very... singular. You wouldn't understand.
Enlighten me then.
- You look beautiful.
- Taylor has good taste.
- What are you doing here later?
- I'm working at the hardware store till 7.
I'll have Taylor pick you up then.
I'd like to bite that lip.
I think I'd like that.
I'm not gonna touch you, not until I have your written consent.
What?
I'll explain later. Come, I'll take you home.
Fuck the paperwork.
What is it about elevators?
Hey!
- Hi, you must be Ana.
- You must be Elliot.
And we must be going, Elliot.
So awesome to meet your. Kate's told me a lot about you.
Elliot, find your shoes, some of us have work to return to.
What you're doing with Mr Worm here, I've got no idea.
Laters baby.
I'll see you tonight, email me if something changes.
My computer's broken.
Well call then, you know you have my number.
Laters, baby.
- Elliot seems really nice.
- No, no. We're starting with you.
If you're seeing him again tonight, this means that something happened.
- Ana? Tell me what happened...
- I have to get ready for work.
We just kissed. Once.
Only once? Thats odd.
- Odd doesn't even cover it.
- Uh huh, and a new jacket.
Bye.
Hi, its Taylor right?
Good evening, Miss Steele, Mr Grey will be joining us there.
Good evening, Anastasia.
What, you're flying this?
No escaping now.
November 1-2-2-4. Charlie Tango. Ready to depart.
Charlie tango, your flight plan to Seattle has been cleared.
Seattle? Thats where we're going?
- Would you like a drink?
- Yes please.
- You play?
- Yes.
Of course you do.
- Whats this?
- Its a nondisclosure agreement.
It means you cannot discuss anything about us with anyone.
I'm afraid my lawyer insists on it.
I would never talk to anyone about us anyway.
Are you gonna make love to me now?
Two things: First, I don't make love.
I fuck hard.
- And the second?
- Come.
- Its just behind this door.
- What is it?
- My playroom.
- Like your xbox and stuff?
Its important you know that you can leave at any time.
Why, what's in there?
I meant what I said, the helicopter
is standby, for whenever you wanna go.
Christian, Just open the door.
Oh my god.
Its called a flogger.
Say something please.
Do women do this to you or...
I do this to women. With women.
Women who want me to.
- You're a sadist?
- I'm a dominant.
What does that mean?
It means I want you to willingly surrender yourself to me.
Why would I do that?
- To please me.
- Please you? How?
I have rules, if you follow them, I'll reward you.
If you don't, I'll punish you.
You'd punish me, you'd use this stuff on me?
- Yes.
- What would I get out of this?
Me.
If we were to do this, this would be your room.
You can decorate it however you like.
You want me to move in?
Not full time, just Friday through to Sunday.
We can negotiate the particulars.
So, I'd sleep in here with you?
No I sleep downstairs. I told you, I don't sleep with anyone.
What if I don't want anything to do with that?
Then I understand completely.
But then we wouldn't have any sort of relationship at all?
This is the only sort of relationship I have.
- Why?
- It's the way I am.
When you said negotiate, what did you mean?
I already have the contract prepared. It's fairly detailed.
You will review it, and we'll negotiate what you are and not willing to try.
How can I know what I'd be willing to try?
Well, when you had sex, was there anything you didn't like doing?
We have to be honest with each other for this to work,
Okay?
- Because I haven't...
- You're still a virgin?
I've just shown you...
I know, I just...
- You've done other things, right?
- No.
- Where have you been?
- Waiting.
Guys must throw themselves at you.
They're never what I've wanted.
You are biting your lip.
- What are you doing?
- Rectifying the situation.
I am a situation?
You're energetic this morning.
- You hungry?
- Very.
Because I'm making pancakes.
Lets get you cleaned up.
Do you trust me?
Stay here.
Hold out your wrists.
Hold them there. Understand?
- Tell me you understand.
- I won't move my arms.
Good girl.
- Stay still.
- Okay.
- Say yes.
- To what.
Being mine.
Christian!
- Shit. - What? - Its my mother.
- I'm naked.
- Get dressed.
No need to show me around, no need to hover.
He's sleeping, Dr. Grey.
Still sleeping? He never sleeps in.
Certainly not at this hour.
Unless of course he's ill is he? Ah.
Sorry Mr. Grey.
Its fine, I know how she can be.
She? Darling you can try to avoid me, but the least you can do is
call me by my correct name, which is mama.
- Hi.
- Oh, dear god.
Mother, Anastasia Steele. Ana, meet my mother.
Dr. Grace, Trevelyan Grey.
You have no idea how delighted I am to meet you.
Its nice to meet you too, Dr. Grey.
Grace. She's very pretty.
You are very pretty.
Thanks.
What happened to calling before dropping by?
And have your head-henchman give me the run around here, no thank you.
I'll take my chances. Well I was in the neighbourhood and I thought perhaps
we could have lunch.
I can't today, I have to drive Ana home.
Its okay, take it, I was just showing mother out.
Excuse me.
Anastasia!
- Kate, wait.
- It was a joy to meet you.
I'm having the whole family next week for dinner at my house.
Christian's sister Mia is back from Paris, you must come.
We'll see, mother.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
Kate.
Thank you.
I can't talk about it right now, Kate.
I gotta go, I'll call you back, okay?
Everything okay with the phone call?
Yeah, nothing important. I liked your mom.
She's excited. She's never seen me with a woman before.
You're the first.
What is it, Ana?
I just... How many women have stayed in here?
15.
- Thats a lot of women.
- I told you before, if you want out...
I don't want out, I just...
I am not exactly jumping at the opportunity
to get your whips, torture and your red room of pain.
The red room is much more about pleasure. I promise you.
Will we still go out to dinner, and movies and...
That's not really my thing.
Try to keep an open mind.
If you agree to be my submissive, I will be devoted to you.
This is what I want. And I want it with you.
Why do I have to sleep in here? We slept in the same bed last night.
Like normal people.
Try not to get hung up on the sleeping arrangements.
If you agree to do this, you're gonna want your own room.
Why, because I'll be your sex slave?
I don't wanna do this here, lets talk downstairs.
No. I think I'll hold on to my freewill a little while longer, thank you.
Actually you know what, I would like to go home, can I go home?
- Which one's yours?
- All of them.
Lets go for a walk.
How did you start doing this?
One of my mother's friends.
- I was 15.
- She seduced you?
I was her submissive for six years.
Seriously, does your mother know that?
Of course not. No one in my family knows about this.
Part of me.
So she introduced you to all of this? Mrs Robinson?
Mrs Robinson? I'll tell her you said that.
She'll love it.
- You still talk to her?
- On occasions. We're friends.
Ana. I know how intimidating this is. I felt the same at first.
By giving up control, I felt free, from responsibilities.
From making decisions. I felt safe.
You will too, you'll see.
I never took anyone in the helicopter.
Never had sex in my own bed. Never slept with anyone.
Ever. Only you.
This is the contract. Read it carefully.
Email me if you have any questions.
I told you, my computer's down.
Just consider it okay?
I really hope you say yes.
- Thanks for the ride.
- Laters baby.
- Um.
- Okay, you're all set.
Your roommate let me in.
I just figured you forgot to tell me about it.
- Do I look okay?
- Tell you about what?
- Just sign here.
- Hold on, do you have the right apartment?
Anastasia Steele?
- Enjoy.
- Another gift huh?
What happened to flowers and chocolate?
I'm dying to hear everything, but
I have to run right now, cause Elliot and I are having dinner.
And then we're seeing a show at the Gorge.
Jose called for you, twice, by the way.
- The mailer had come?
- Oh um...
These are my thesis notes, I left them at school.
Oh okay, well there's yesterday's mail.
- What?
- I don't know. You look... different.
- I feel different.
- Of course you do.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Bye.
The following are the terms of a binding contract...
Between the dominant and the submissive. The fundamental purpose of this contract...
Is to allow the submissive to explore her sensuality, and her limits of safeness.
The dominant and the submissive agree and acknowledge that all that occurs
under the terms of this contract will be consensual,
confidential.
And subject to the agreed limits and safety procedures set out in this contract.
The submissive will agree to any
sexual activity deemed fit and pleasurable by the dominant,
Excepting those activities, outlined in Hard Limits.
So much. Thank you.
The Submissive will not drink to excess, smoke, or take recreational drugs,
or put her person into any unnecessary risk.
The Submissive will not enter into sexual relations
with anyone other than the Dominant.
The Submissive agrees to procure oral contraception
from a physician of the Dominant's choosing.
The Submissive will eat regularly
to maintain her health and well-being
from a prescribed list of foods. Appendix Four.
The Submissive will obey any instruction given by the Dominant.
She will do so eagerly and without hesitation.
The Submissive may not touch the Dominant
without his expressed permission to do so.
The Submissive shall always conduct herself
in a respectful manner to the Dominant,
And she'll address him only as "Sir," "Mr. Grey..."
or such other title as the Dominant may direct.
The Dominant may flog, spank, whip, or corporally punish the Submissive
As he sees fit, for purposes of discipline
Or for his personal enjoyment.
The safe word yellow
will be used to bring the attention of the dominant
that the submissive is close to her limit.
When the safe word Red is spoken.
The dominantes actions will cease completely
and immediately.
Submissive.
Does the submissive agree to be restrained, with hands bound?
Does the submissive consent to being blindfolded?
Does the submissive consent to be gagged?
How much pain is the submissive willing to experience?
Christian.
Its been nice knowing me has it?
Let me remind you, how nice it was.
Is this what you want?
Don't make a sound.
Was this "nice"?
That was really nice.
Mr Christian Grey: Dominant.
Miss Anastasia Steele: Submissive.
What are you doing to me?
What about here?
Why not? Is that breaking the rules?
- Speaking of which...- I haven't made up my mind yet.
- You're not staying?
- I told you. I don't sleep with anyone.
Can we negotiate?
Thats a hell of a sack, Miss Steele.
Business meeting.
- Impressive.- I've done this before.
- Business meetings I mean.
- Oh.
Miss Steele. Your meeting.
Page 1... strike out my old address and replace it with the new one.
An oversight. Do go on.
Page 3, section 15-20.
"The submissive shall submit to any sexual activity"
"... demanded by the dominant without hesitation or argument."
Turn to page 5, appendix 3, soft limits.
- With you.- Find anal fisting.
- I'm all ears.- Strike it out.
Strike out vaginal fisting too.
- You sure?
- Yep.
Same page.
"Is the use of sex toys acceptable to the submissive."
Vibrators... okay, Dildos... fine.
Genital clamps... absolutely not.
- Consider them gone.- What are butt plugs?
You must go through quite a few non-disclosure agreements.
My staff know only what I choose to tell them.
Please resume Miss Steele.
Also, on page 5, there are some terms which need clarification.
- Suspension?
- Hanging on a rope from the ceiling.
- For what possible reason?
- For your pleasure.
- Really?
- And mine... something to consider.
No. Hard limit.
"Is bondage acceptable to the submissive?"... I'm good with rope.
Leather casts, hand cuffs... Please lose tape.
- And whats others?
- Cable ties?
Can I just say how impressed I am with your commitment to this meeting?
And in that spirit, I'm gonna offer something sweeter.
How about, once a week, on a night of your choosing, we go on a date.
Just like a regular couple... dinner movie, ice skating.
- Whatever you want.
- Accepted.
- You're very kind.- I'll suggest it in Appendix 5.
I would like to fuck you into the middle of next week.
- You're not fighting fair.- I never have.
I'll review all these changes and try to arrive at a decision.
- You wanna leave?
- Yes.
But your body tells me something different. Your legs for instance.
The way you're pressing your thighs together under the table.
The change in your breathing. And then your complexion.
- My complexion?
- You're flushed.
- That could just be the wine.- Its the adrenaline.
Say I did stay. What would happen?
First, I would help you out of that little dress of yours.
- Yes?
- Then I'd be pleased to discover...
- that you are naked underneath.- Really?
- Then I would bend you over.- Right here?
- Yes.- On this table?
Yes.
Thank you for the meeting, Mr. Grey.
This is me.
Didn't know I was a collector of classic cars huh?
You're sure I can't persuade you to stay?
Goodnight, Christian.
- When will you know?
- Soon, maybe.
Why do I think you're telling me goodbye?
Because I'm leaving.
You got your speech ready yet?
More or less.
- Annie.
- Dad!
Hi.
Sorry I'm late, I had a hell of a time parking.
Oh thats okay, you're here, that's all that matters.
You're kidding me, I wouldn't miss this for the world.
I saved you a seat next to Kate's parents, okay?
- I'll sit where you want, Miss Steele.
- Okay. I'll see you after.
Yeah, good luck out there.
And is also a major benefactor for our university.
Please join me in welcoming, Mr Christian Grey.
Thank you. I am deeply moved by the great compliment accorded to me today.
- He is so hot.
- Oh god. He so is.
I heard he's gay.
Sustainable methods of farming for third world countries.
The goal? To eradicate hunger and poverty across the globe.
I myself have known what its like to be profoundly hungry.
So this is a very personal mission for me.
Anastasia Steele.
Thanks.
Congratulations, you must be very proud.
I am. Nice tie by the way?
Truthfully its become my favourite.
- Do you have your answer yet?
- I'm still thinking.
Anastasia, just try it my way. Please.
- Okay.
- What?
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Dad, hi!
- I am so proud of you, Annie.
Thank you.
Oh, Kate. Best speech of all others.
- Thanks.
- Of course.
Yeah, I agree.
- Ana? Hi.
- Hi.
Ray, have you met Christian Grey? Ana's new boyfriend?
Hi.
Great pleasure to meet you.
My pleasure. I really enjoyed your speech.
Thank you, sir.
Sounds like you've accomplished some pretty impressive things.
And what things?
- Thank you.
- Okay, I'm gonna go find my family,
who are impatiently waiting to embarrass me. Bye.
- Visit us soon, yeah?
- Soon as I get an invitation.
So, how long you two known each other?
A few weeks now, we actually met when Anastasia
interviewed me for the student newspaper.
- A picture please Mr. Grey?
- One minute excuse me.
Big smile now.
To celebrate your graduation. Among other things.
Roll your eyes at me again, and I will take you across my knee.
So it begins.
- Come on, I've got something to show you.
- What?
Thats cute. Doesn't really seem like your style though.
It's not, happy graduation, Anastasia.
Oh my god. Christian, thats a car.
You don't miss much, do you?
Thank you but I can't. This is too...
- Do you like it?
- Of course I like it, its beautiful.
But I have a car... Where's my car?
I told Taylor to fetch a decent price for it.
Christian, this is way too much.
Did you just roll your eyes at me?
Do you know why I'm doing this?
Because I rolled my eyes at you.
And is that polite?
No.
- Excuse me?
- No, sir.
- Do you want more?
- Yes. Yes.
Welcome to my world.
- What are you doing?
- There a few things at the office
which require my attention.
You okay?
- I just thought that...
- I enjoyed tonight.
I'll see you at my place tomorrow.
Hi, mama.
Anastasia? Whats going on, I've left you two messages this week.
I know I'm sorry. I just got a little distracted.
I'm sorry I missed your graduation honey, I heard it was lovely.
And your new beau.
Ray told me all about him, he sounds such a young man.
Of course, I would've preferred to have heard about it from you.
Ana?
Whats the matter?
Nothing, I'm fine.
Is he not making you happy?
He is yeah, I mean most of the time, yeah.
Its complicated.
Listen honey, if you need a break, you just
come on right down here.
Even if its just for a day or two.
I have air miles, and we could talk and have girl time.
Promise me you'll think about it?
Yeah I promise. I promise.
- I love you mama.
- I love you too darling.
I gotta go. Bye.
Looks like you and Grey did some celebration last night.
- Is he still asleep?
- No, he couldn't stay.
Well whose car keys are those then?
- Those are my keys.
- Wow Ana.
What?
Nothing, I'm just...
Make sure you're taking it at your own pace okay?
I am, I am, I gotta go.
Where are you going?
- Look at this.
- I've seen it, not a bad picture.
Christian Grey and friend.
So we're friends.
Well it must be true, if its in the paper.
- So how did it go with Dr. Greene?
- It was fine.
But she said I had to abstain from
all sexual activity for four weeks.
You know, after I start the pill.
What?
Just kidding.
I wanna take you to my playroom.
I haven't signed the contract.
I'm well aware. Call it due diligence.
Okay.
Ready?
Eyes down. Take off your shoes.
Arms above your head.
You have a beautiful body, Anastasia.
I want you unashamed of your nakedness, understand?
Yes sir.
You're biting your lip, you know what it does to me. Turn around.
When I tell you to come into this room. This is how you'll be.
You'll wait for me.
Kneeling by the door.
Hands flat on your thighs. Good.
Hold out your hands.
- Did that hurt?
- No.
You see? Much of your fear is in your head.
Come.
- How does that feel?
- Good, sir.
Quiet.
Where are we going?
Remember my mother mentioned dinner?
My sister Mia's in town.
Yes.
- You got everything you need?
- Yeah.
Dance with me.
- Good evening, Mr. Grey.
- Hi.
They're here!
You're here.
- Welcome welcome.
- Ana, you've met my mother.
Hi, lovely to see you.
- This is my father, Carrick.
- Hi, it's nice to meet you.
Pleasure to meet you.
Is she here?
There's been a lot of speculation!
Oh my god! She exists!
Its a great apartment, and the rent's not ridiculous.
Elliot and Jose helped us move in.
Jose is Ana's friend,
although I think Elliot's trying to poach him.
He's a cool guy!
Ana, where is your family from?
My step father's in Montesano and my mom lives in Georgia.
- Georgia? Which part?
- Savannah.
How nice! Although I hear it gets really humid in Georgia this time of year.
Oh my god it does. Its stifling sometimes.
Actually I'm going to visit her tomorrow.
How nice. You hear that Christian?
Some children do visit their parents now and again.
Hey dad, you catch the Mariners game?
I heard it went back stream.
Ugh. Seattle baseball...
This is news to me.
When were you gonna tell me?
Who wants coffee?
Actually I promised Ana a tour of the grounds.
Excuse us.
Christian, I cannot walk that fast in these shoes.
When were you gonna tell me about Georgia?
What? You have no right to be mad at me.
Yeah but I am mad. Palm-twitchingly mad.
You're mine. All mine. Understand?
Christian, you're so confusing.
- Ana.
- What do you want?
- I want you.
I'm trying, Christian.
I know you are.
Why can't we sleep in the same bed?
Why won't you let me touch you? Why does it have to be like this?
If you would just sign the contract, you wouldn't have...
Why do you care so much about the contract, Christian?
- Don't you like me the way I am?
- Of course I do.
- Then why are you trying to change me?
- I'm not.
- Its you...
- I need more, I want more.
Hearts and flowers? That's not something I know.
Ana please... Its you that is changing me.
Let me touch you. Let me.
- Are they burns?
- I had a rough start in life.
- That's all you need to know.- Okay.
The woman who gave birth to me, was a crack addict.
And a prostitute.
She died when I was four.
I remember certain things. Terrible things.
I don't remember her.
Sometimes, I can see her in my dreams.
Do you really have to go to Georgia?
Yeah, I really.
Good morning. 12-H is down to your right.
Good morning. 2-B, oh it's just right here.
Oh! No, I'm supposed to be in coach.
Oh, you must have been upgraded.
Good morning. 12-A just down to your right.
Good morning.
- This gazpacho is really salty, Bob.
- Yeah.
You'll get fat with all this sitting around. You tell him, Ana.
Now could you hand me some chips for my bowl of salsa?
You can have a carrot?
What are you getting at with this?
You're lucky that I happen to love you very much.
- I know that.
- Do you?
Hmm, I do.
Oh darling, I think we should pace ourselves,
or at least order something to eat.
You go ahead, I'm not very hungry.
Oh, I just have the fruit salad.
- He can wait.
- Mom.
ANOTHER COSMO?
- Holy fuck.
- What?
What is it?
Its Christian, he's here, in Georgia.
- Here, here!
- Mrs Adams,
delighted to meet you.
- Something to drink sir?
- Gin and tonic.
Hendrix if you have it, otherwise Bombay Sapphire.
Cucumber with the Hendricks, lime with Bombay.
I like him already.
What are you doing here, Christian?
- I came to see you.
- I need to go to the bathroom.
I broke rule 7, clause 5.
We'll let it go, lets not talk about the contract right now.
How was your dinner?
She's a friend, thats all.
She's a child abuser.
I confide in her.
She knows me.
- What did she advise you to do?
- Well, I'm here.
- Now what?
- I've got a room in this hotel.
Well, I hope you'll be comfortable in it.
What are you doing for breakfast tomorrow?
- Where are we going?
- It's a surprise.
I think I've reached my quota of surprises.
We're almost there.
Mr Grey. Hey, I'll be your co-pilot.
How do you do? This is my girlfriend, Anastasia Steele.
We're at 400 feet, ready?
- Ready?
- Yes, ready.
Release.
Hold on tight.
- Is this more?
- Oh my god. So much more!
Oh my god, that was incredible, Christian. Thank you.
We aim to please, Miss Steele.
- I thought you didn't do romance.
- I don't. Ana.
What? What? Why are you fighting this?
What are you afraid of?
Grey. What? When?
Have Stefan get the plane ready. I'll be on the tarmac in 30 minutes.
- What happened?
- I have to go back to Seattle.
Come I'll take you home.
Oh sweetheart, I wish Christian could've stayed.
Bob was looking forward to meeting him.
I know, he had to get back to Seattle though. There's a um, situation at work.
I wish I could tell you things get easier, but they don't.
You just need to get to know yourself better.
- Thank you for everything, mama.
- Take care, sweetheart.
I will.
You think I wouldn't recognise you, Taylor?
Right this way, Miss Steele.
- How does he seem today, Taylor?
- Preoccupied I'm afraid.
- Really?
- Yes ma'am.
Well, that's not gonna work.
What?
Well tell them they don't have 24 hours. That is unnacceptable.
I need to know. Just keep me informed.
- Is everything okay?
- Nothing that concerns you.
- I can leave if you want me to go?
- No.
Thats the last thing I want.
I want you, in the playroom, in 15 minutes.
- What are your safe words?
- Red and yellow.
Remember them.
That sounds so sad. Everything you played is so sad.
You said you were six when you learn
with it, because you wanted to please your new family?
I just wanna talk.
Why won't you let me in?
- We should be talking.
- Like normal people?
Yeah.
Is that so wrong?
Is this because of the contract? Because I still haven't signed it?
Fuck the contract, I think its a little redundant, don't you?
So then the rules are redundant too?
- No. The rules stand.
- And what if I break them?
- Then there'll be consequences.
- Punishment?
Yes.
- Why do you want to punish me?
- Ana.
Why do you want to hurt me?
I would never do anything to you, that you couldn't handle.
But why do you even wanna do anything at all to me, Christian?
If I told you, you'd never look at me the same way again.
So there is a reason. Tell me.
- Do you wanna punish me right now?
- Yes.
I wanna punish you right now.
What if I told you that I feel the same way about being punished as you
do about me touching you, would you still wanna punish me then?
No. But that doesn't mean I wouldn't need to.
- Why?
- Ana stop.
- Why do you need...
- Because it's the way I am!
Because I'm 50 shades of fucked up.
Show me then.
I need you to show me, what you wanna do to me.
Punish me, show me how bad it can be.
I want you to show me the worst.
It's the only way I can understand.
- Are you sure about this?
- Yes.
Bend over.
I'm gonna hit you six times. And you're gonna count with me.
- Count, Anastasia.
- One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
No! Don't fucking touch me.
Is this what you really want? You wanna see me like this?
- Ana.
- Don't come near me.
Does this give you pleasure?
No.
Don't you dare come near me.
Please don't hate me.
You will never do that to me again.
- I'm not what you want.
- No, you are everything that I want.
I've fallen in love with you.
No. No, Ana. You can't love me.
I need you to leave.
Please.
- I'd like my car back.
- Taylor already sold it.
Then I'd like the money he got for it please.
I'll send you a check.
Okay.
Taylor will take you home.
Stop.
No!
- Ana.
- Christian.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org